Brihan Batitusta

Ambarawa, Central Java, Indonesia 🗷 brihanbatitusta77@gmail.com 🛘 087879510032 🛅 www.linkedin.com/in/brihan-batitusta-9057b8249

SUMMARY

I am a fresh graduate of Bachelor of Communication Science from Soegijapranata University with a focus on journalism and media industry. As a passionate fresh graduate of communication science, I have a great desire to succeed in the media and digital marketing industry. My expertise in photo and video editing, as well as proficiency in Microsoft Excel, HTML, and CSS, allow me to be a valuable asset in dealing with the ever-evolving demands of the digital world. I am ready to bring my creativity and technical skills to the professional world to deliver inspiring content and effective marketing strategies.

EXPERIENCE

Barista

Kulo Coffee Shop

February 2018 - October 2020, Semarang City

- · Memorized several menu recipes and served them to customers while interacting with customers.
- · Explain the menu to customers and offer monthly promotions.
- · Manage and be responsible for daily revenue.

Media Literacy Agent (Internship)

Komisi Penyiaran Indonesia Daerah Jawa Tengah

January 2020 - March 2020, Semarang City

- · Supervise the content of television broadcasts and record violations found in accordance with applicable guidelines.
- · Participate in evaluation hearings

Waiter

Pandanaran Hotel

March 2017 - June 2017, Semarang City

- · Deliver food and beverages to customers and ensure orders are as requested.
- · Assist in decorating rooms used for specific events.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Communication Science

Minor in Journalism and Media Industry · University Of Soegijapranata · Semarang · 2023

 \cdot Earned a 4-year scholarship thanks to his non-academic achievements in sports.

COURSEWORK

Responsive Web Design

freeCodeCamp \cdot 2023 \cdot HTML and CSS

Digital Marketing Fundamental

Myskill · 2023

Microsoft Excel

Myskill · 2023 · Data Visualization

Human Resources

Myskill · 2023 · Job Analysis Process

Digital Marketing Specialization

Rakamin Academy • 2023 • Content Pillar Social Media

Fullstack Web Development Specialization

Rakamin Academy · 2023 · HTML and CSS

INVOLVEMENT

Equipment Committe

University Katolik Soegijapranata • FHK Day 2019 • September 2019 - September 2023

· Prepare, procure, and be responsible for the equipment used during the event.

Leader Of Basketball Student Activity Unit

University Soegijapranata · Basketball Student Activity Unit · September 2018 - September 2019

· Develop and manage the UKM budget, to finance UKM activities.

- Submitting requests for proposals for activity funding assistance.
- · Responsible for the activities carried out

Equipment Committe

University Soegijapranata • Soegijapranata Basketball League 2019 • January 2019 - March 2019

- Prepare the necessary equipment
- Source and arrange equipment rental contracts.
- Conduct equipment rental negotiations

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office
- HTML & CSS
- Editing Image & Video (Canva,Lightroom,Capcut,VN)